{
    "subject": "Edna_Manley",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Norman_Manley",
    "human_readable": "Edna Manley is married to Norman Manley.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9861512780189514,
            "question": "Are Edna Manley and Norman Manley a married couple?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9624968767166138,
            "question": "To whom is Edna Manley married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9546770453453064,
            "question": "Is Norman Manley married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9506382942199707,
            "question": "Who is Edna Manley married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9175203442573547,
            "question": "Name the husband of Edna Manley."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8983904719352722,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Edna Manley and Norman Manley?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7986494302749634,
            "question": "What is the name of Edna Manley's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7815122604370117,
            "question": "Who is Norman Manley?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6475533246994019,
            "question": "What familial connection exists between Edna Manley and Norman Manley?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18818862736225128,
            "question": "Who are the spouses in this relationship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Edna Manley is married to Norman Manley.",
            "html": "yago_9712_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What familial connection exists between Edna Manley and Norman Manley?",
            "html": "yago_9712_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Norman Manley?",
            "html": "yago_9712_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Edna Manley's husband?",
            "html": "yago_9712_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9712_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9712_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9712_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9712_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9712_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9712_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9712_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9712_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9712_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9712_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Edna Manley was married to Norman Manley. For instance, the document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_9712/re-ranker-msmarco/37.txt mentions \"It is written by her granddaughter, Rachel Manley, who was part of her grandmother\u2019s life both in England, where Edna was born, and later in Jamaica where Edna went when she married Norman Manley.\" This directly supports the statement that Edna Manley is married to Norman Manley."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}